Lesson four.
Repetition drill.
Look at lesson four.
Look and listen.
Do not speak.
Look at number one.
Is this your pen?
Yes, it is.
Look at number two.
Is this your pencil?
Yes, it is,
Look at number three.
Is this your book?
Yes, it is,
Now you ask the questions.
Ready?
Look at number one.
Is this your pen?
Yes it is.
Look at number two.
Is this your pencil?
Yes it is.
Look at number three,
Is this your book?
Yes it is.
Look at number four.
Is this your watch?
Yes, it is,
Look at number five,
Is this your coat?
No.
It isn't.
Look at number six.
Is this your dress?
Yes, it is.
Look at number seven.
Is this your skirt?
No it isn't.
Look at number eight.
Is this your shirt?
Yes, it is.
Look at number nine.
Is this your car?
Yes, it is.
Look at number ten.
Is this your house?
No, it isn't.
Look at number eleven.
Is this your suit?
Yes, it is,
Look at number 12.
Is this your school?
No, it isn't.
Look at number thirteen.
Is this your teacher?
Yes, it is.
Look at number fourteen.
Is this your son?
No, it isn't.
Look at number fifteen.