Lesson 2.
repetition drill.
Look at lesson 2.
Look and listen.
Do not speak.
Look at number one.
Is this your pen?
Yes, it is.
Look at number two.
Is this your pencil?
Yes, it is.
Look at number 3.
Is this your book?
Yes, it is.
Now you ask the questions.
ready.
Look at number one.
Is this your pen?
Yes, it is.
Look at number two.
Is this your pencil?
Yes, it is.
Look at number three.
Is this your book?
Yes, it is.
Look at number 4.
Is this your watch?
Yes, it is.
Look at number five.
Is this your coat?
Yes, it is.
Look at number 6.
Is this your dress?
Yes, it is.
Look at number 7.
Is this your skirt?
Yes, it is.
Look at number eight.
Is this your shirt?
Yes, it is.
Look at number 9.
Is this your car?
Yes, it is.
Look at number 10.
Is this your house?