Lesson six.
Repetition dwell.
Look at lesson six.
Look and listen.
Do not speak.
Look at number eight.
That's a vol
Is it a Swedish car?
Or a French car.
It isn't a French car, it's a Swedish car.
Look at number nine.
That's a Peugeot.
Is it a French car?
Or a Swedish car.
It isn't a Swedish car, it's a French car.
Look at number ten.
That's a Mercedes.
Is it a German car?
Or a Japanese car.
It isn't a Japanese car.
It's a German car.
Now you answer the questions in the same way
Ready?
Look at number eight.
That's a Vovel.
Is it a Swedish car?
Or a French car.
It isn't a French car, it's a Swedish car.
Look at number nine.
That's a pejot. Is it a Fren car or a Swedish car?
It isn't a Swedish car, it's a French car.
Look at number ten.
That's a Mercedes.
Is it a German car?
Or a Japanese car.
It isn't a Japanese car, but
It's a German car.
Look at number eleven.
That's a Toyota.
Is it a Japanese car?
Or a German car.
It isn't a German car. It's a Japanese car.
Look at number twelve.
That's a day woo.
Is it a British car?
Or a Korean car.
It isn't a British car, it's a Korean car.
Look at number thirteen.
That's a mini
Is it an American car?
Or an English car.
It isn't an American car. It's an English car.
Look at number fourteen.
That's a Ford.
Is it a Swedish car?
Or an American car.
It isn't a Swedish car.
It's an American car.
Look at number 15.
That's a fiat.
Is it an Italian car?
Or an American car.
It isn't an American car.